(Amy:)Sheldon, it's a routine
procedure.
(Amy:)I've heard you complain
about his snoring.
We... Yes, for the first
five or six years,
(Sheldon:)but I've gotten used to it.
(Sheldon:)It helps me sleep.
(Sheldon:)He's like my mucus-powered
white noise machine.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I'm gonna get
the surgery, it's no big deal.
(Leonard:)End of story.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
I'm done talking about it.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
I believe it was
your turn in the game.
(Amy:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Let's see...
(Sheldon:)Oh, this person is most famous
(Sheldon:)for never having gotten
(Sheldon:)his nose mutilated
with elective surgery
(Sheldon:)and never living the rest
of his life in the shadows
(Sheldon:)as a hideous, disfigured freak.
(Leonard:)I think you could
give a better clue.
(Sheldon:)I don't.
(Sheldon:)I'm not even sure if
that's a person or a typo.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪